

## CONTACT ME AT



Pune, Maharashtra



ajayakumbhar1234@gmail.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/ajaykumbhar

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

Machine Learning, Deep Learning Tensorflow, Keras, Sklearn, Python HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Boostrap Angular, React Node, Express MySql, MongoDB

## CERTIFICATION

Machine Learning - Datacamp Deep Learning - Datacamp Hacker Rank Python Full Stack Developer (MEAN) React Bootcamp

## CO - CURRICULAR

Member of CESA 2020 Member of CESA 2019 Member of PR 2020

## HOBBIES

Guitar Player Cooking



# **KUMBHAR AJAY**

# DATA ANALYTICS | FULL STACK DEVLOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Motivated, teamwork-oriented, and responsible Data Analyst with significant experience in increasing comprehension of reports and presentations by the average professional. Also have more than 1 year industry experience as web developer. Work more than 3 companies as web developer and held great knowledge of working with industry and people within it.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Intern

Milliman India, Jan 2021 - March 2021

- Develop Fully Functional SAS product for health industry.
- Responsible for Whole Front end application Development.

## Intern, MEAN Stack

Travel Toggle, Jun 2020 - Sep 2020

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Collaborated with other designers
- Implemented Agile development process across all teams

### Intern, MEAN Stack

Wisdom Sprouts Training and development, Jan 2020 - May 2020

- Learn to build full stack application with the help of MEAN stack.
- Develop e-commerce application for test skill in MEAN stack.

# EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

#### B.E

Savitribai Phule Pune University, 2017-Present

CGPA: 8.2

#### **HSC**

State Board Maharashtra, 2016-2017

Yashwantrao Chavan Institute of Science, Satara

Percentage: 81.23

#### SSC

State Board Maharashtra, 2014-2015

Dr B. J. Date Prashala Natepute

Percentage: 90.60